詹傑宇

CHAN, CHIEH-YU

Email: jk29666338@gmail.com

Github: github.com/JYu1999

Website: jyu1999.com

CHIEH-YU is currently a **backend developer** working at *Amastek*. Additionally, he serves as an **associate mentor** at *GoodIdea Studio Backend Camp*.

He completed his studies at *National Tsing Hua University in June 2022*. During his studies, he used to be the **lead developer** for a VR gaming project as part of his coursework. Furthermore, he assumed the role of **project manager** for a VR boxing training software.

To further enhance his backend development skills, CHIEH-YU joined Goodldea Studio Backend Camp after graduating. He has a keen interest in the areas of backend development, and continually expanding his knowledge and skills in this field.

Experience

May 2023 - Present

Backend Developer 森淨科技(AmasTek)

- Planning system architecture, system logic, database design
- Develop customized software to assist customers in digital transformation with Ruby on Rails
- Responsible for writing technical development related documents

Apr 2023 - May 2023

Intern 泰峻系統科技(Tech-genes)

- Investigating the Laravel packages used by the company, such as Livewire and Backpack.
- Supporting the company in implementing a business process management system.

Projects



Website: Personal Blog

A personal blog built with Laravel.

More Info.



VR Application: Boxing basic movement training and live target simulation tool

More Info.

Education

GoodIdea Studio

Backend Camp

2022/11 - 2023/04

- · Learning backend related skills, including:
 - Language: PHP, Javascript, SQL
 - o Framework: Laravel
 - o Tools: Git, Postman
 - OS: MacOS, Linux(ubuntu)
 - o Cloud Host: AWS

National Tsing Hua University

Interdisciplinary Program of Engineering

2018/9 - 2022/6

• Programming related courses

- Fundamental: Introduction to Programming Languages (C), Data Structures(C++), Design and Analysis of Algorithms
- **Internet**: Introduction to Computer Networks
- **Hardware**: Operating Systems, Computer Architecture, Logic Design
- **Application**: Introduction to Game Programming (C#), Virtual Reality(C#), Information and Communication Technologies in Smart Manufacturing

Certifications

TOEFL IBT 95